Jennifer Kiesler

Sun Prairie, WI Phone: (262) 994-8243 Email: kiesler.jen@gmail.com LinkedIn Portfolio

Summary

Currently enrolled in a coding bootcamp where I have developed many applications independently and as part of a group. I have acquired many transferable skills from my previous work experiences including problem-solving, communication, and time management that will allow me to excel in the workplace.

| _ | | | |
|-----|-------|-------|-----|
| | กทเกล | I GVI | 110 |
| ICU | hnica | I ONI | 113 |

| | | 1 oommour ommo | | | | |
|---|-----------------|------------------------------------|--------------------|------------------------|--|--|
| Visual Studio | HTML | jQuery | Node.js | Jest | | |
| GitHub | CSS | Bootstrap | OOP | Express.js | | |
| Git Bash | JavaScript | REST APIs | TDD | MySQL | | |
| Additional Skills | | | | | | |
| Problem-solving | | Time management | Organization | | | |
| Collaboration | | Ability to work under pressure | ssure Multitasking | | | |
| Communication | ١ | Adaptability | | Decision-making | | |
| | | Education | | | | |
| University of Wisconsin Coding Bootcamp | | | | Expected February 2023 | | |
| Currently enrolled | - | | | | | |
| University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee (Milwaukee, WI) | | | | May 2018 | | |
| Biology and Chemistry Te | eaching Certifi | cations | | | | |
| University of Wisconsin-L | | May 2014 | | | | |
| | | or, Cellular/Molecular Emphasis, (| Chemistry M | | | |

Professional Experience

Science Teacher, Marshall High School (Marshall, WI)

August 2020-June 2021

- Taught students the required curriculum in the allotted time frame
- Collaborated with co-workers to discuss different teaching methods
- Analyzed and reflected on lessons
- Made decisions on what teaching methods would work best for each individual student/class
- Adapted to teaching remote and in-class students at the same time

Science Teacher, Denmark High School (Denmark, WI)

August 2019-May 2020

- Taught students the required curriculum in the allotted time frame
- Collaborated with co-workers to create curriculums
- Adapted to teaching remotely

Science Teacher, MC² High School (Milwaukee, WI)

August 2018-June 2019

- Taught students the required curriculum in the allotted time frame
- Analyzed and reflected on lessons
- Created the science curriculum

Research Associate, Aurora Health Care (Milwaukee, WI)

June 2016-June 2017

- Collaborated with co-workers on results from different experiments
- Communicated the results to the Scientist I was working for
- Performed everything that was required each day on time
- Made decisions on the proper method for processing different tumor samples and maintaining tissue cultures

Associate Research Specialist, UW - Madison (Madison, WI)

September 2015-April 2016

- Trained graduate and undergraduate students
- Performed everything that was required each day on time
- Communicated the results to the Scientist I was working for